<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>001. How to get started?</title>
		<description>Discuss 001. How to get started?</description>
		<link>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 05:18:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<generator>JComments</generator>
		<atom:link href="https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/jcomments/rss/com_content/58.php" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<item>
			<title>Maltepe Nakliyat says:</title>
			<link>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-1231</link>
			<description><![CDATA[?stanbulun Maltepe ilçesinde evden eve tas?mac?l?k yap?l?r http://maltepeevdenevenakliyat.eu ekibi]]></description>
			<dc:creator>Maltepe Nakliyat</dc:creator>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 18:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-1231</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jackson Sippe says:</title>
			<link>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-879</link>
			<description><![CDATA[When I tried to run the file an error occurred saying that the version of the file wasn't compatible with my window. By the way I am running windows 7]]></description>
			<dc:creator>Jackson Sippe</dc:creator>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 15:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-879</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>kksou says:</title>
			<link>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-80</link>
			<description><![CDATA[Hi, Yes, PHP-GTK2 sits on top of PHP. So you can use the mysql and oracle DLL that works with standard PHP. However, there are now a lot more open-source web-based PHP libraries for the things you want to do - file sharing ,chatting and more network related things, etc. Also, you can look into very established PHP platform such as Joomla or Drupal which will save you a lot of time. Another point is about maintenance. Web-based applications are so much easier to maintain. You only need to update your server apps, and the rest of the 2000pcs simply uses standard web browser. For PHP-GTK2, it's a client-server architecture. What this means is that while your mysql database can reside at your data server, you need to install client app on each of the 2000 machines! Though you can definitely automate this through some scripts, if you can go with web-based applications, I would strongly recommend you to do so. We use PHP-GTK2 when a web-based application does not work e.g. if you need real-time interface to some MIDI or photographic instruments to read real-time data or to control devices in real-time via serial or parallel ports. Of course you can achieve all these with .NET or C++. But if you only know PHP, and you really need to develop a real-time cross-platform GUI app, PHP-GTK2 is a good choice. Regards, /kksou]]></description>
			<dc:creator>kksou</dc:creator>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 06:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-80</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Pherry says:</title>
			<link>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-79</link>
			<description><![CDATA[Thanks kksou :-) But I have one more question... Our team is going to start a Project which include file sharing ,chatting and more network related things over University network which include about 2000 pc's. So is it good idea to start with php-gtk2 and can i use oracle or mysql as backend. Thanks Pherry]]></description>
			<dc:creator>Pherry</dc:creator>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 03:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-79</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>kksou says:</title>
			<link>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-78</link>
			<description><![CDATA[Hi, By the way, you can also view PHP-GTK as a gtk+ port for PHP. There is also a port for Python: http://www.pygtk.org/ with a much stronger and active group of users there. Regards, /kksou]]></description>
			<dc:creator>kksou</dc:creator>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 15:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-78</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>kksou says:</title>
			<link>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-77</link>
			<description><![CDATA[Hi, PHP-GTK is an extension of PHP. As the name suggests, it's PHP plus GTK+. (GTK+is a cross-platform graphical user interface library which has been around for more than 10 years.) More info here: 1) http://gtk.php.net/ 2) http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PHP-GTK 3) http://www.gtk.org/ 4) http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/GTK%2B The PHP that you've been using are for your web servers in a web environment. On the other hand, PHP-GTK is used to develop standalone desktop applications (similar to all your windows applications e.g. notepad or Microsoft Word) without going through a web browser. You current PHP will not be able to run PHP-GTK because it does not have the php-gtk dll loaded. To run PHP-GTK, you need to download the compiled windows binary version from: http://gtk.php.net/download.php Most of us running PHP-GTK will have 2 copies of PHP on our machine - one for the web server, the other for PHP-GTK. Each of them uses its own PHP.ini for different setup and to load different DLLs. Also, currently all your PHP apps are run from web browser. For PHP-GTK, it's usually run from the command prompt. If you cannot think of any reasons why you would run an application from a command prompt, then most likely you do not need PHP-GTK. But if you need to say control hardware deviccs via your computer, and you want to provide some graphical user interface instead of plain command prompt, PHP-GTK is a good choice, especially if you already have a huge collection of PHP libraries. Hope this gives you a slightly better picture of PHP-GTK. Regards, /kksou]]></description>
			<dc:creator>kksou</dc:creator>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 15:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-77</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Pherry says:</title>
			<link>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-76</link>
			<description><![CDATA[Hi , I am using Xampp for my project ,but problem is that it is not working it gives error "Fatal error: Class 'GtkWindow' not found in D:\Program Files\xampp\xampp\htdocs\Outpass\majak.php on line 101" I am new to this and don't know if i have to make any chane to my current php version AND one more thing Is it also a programming scripting language or it is a programming language. Sorry if i asked anything foolish]]></description>
			<dc:creator>Pherry</dc:creator>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 11:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://kksou.com/php-gtk2/sample-codes/get-started.php#comment-76</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
